cnitv.net 2010-12-26

# Privacy & Security : Worship Network

**Privacy/Security Policy**

The Worship Network always uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server.

**Returns, Exchanges and Refunds**

The Worship Network offers a 30 day return, exchange and or refund on all purchases. Please call 800-728-8723 for more information or email info@worship.net

**Credit card safety**

Ordering online with us is a secure transaction. All online transactions in The Worship Network’s online stores are handled with industry-standard SSL encryption. This means that when you enter your credit card number into the order form, it is transmitted across the Internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets to us. We do not store your credit card information in our database or on our servers.

**E-mail addresses**

When you provide The Worship Network with your email address, we will use it only for the purpose for which it was provided. We do not rent, sell, or exchange your email address with any third party except to provide the services you request or as required by law.

**Information we collect**

When you visit The Worship Network website, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged as it is at most websites, which may include information about your IP address, domain name, browser type, access time, and referring website address. This information is not personally identifiable and is only used in aggregate (not in any way that personally identifies you).

Personally identifiable information is any information about you as an individual that would enable seomone to contact you; for example, your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

The Worship Network will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it. Providing any personally identifiable information to The Worship Network is voluntary. If you do not want The Worship Network to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, do not submit it.

**How we use this information**

Personally identifiable information will be used for the purposes for which it was given. We may also use it to notify you about updates to our website and to contact you for marketing purposes.

You can visit and browse The Worship Network’s websites without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself.

The Worship Network offers free email newsletters. We gather email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Subscribers may change their subscribed email address, opt out of receiving special emailed offers, or remove themselves from any mailing list by following the instructions contained in every newsletter.

**Worship Network – The Christian Network Inc.  
PO Box 681329  
Franklin, TN 37068  
phone 800-728-8723  
email info@worship.net**
